<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-21T11:17:02+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html"> </title><subtitle>Jawatan Kosong Hotel. Malaysia hotel jobs 2020 / 2021</subtitle><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">Inter Island Manpower Pte Ltd Vacancies Chef Management Trainee</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/chef-management-traine-inter-island-manpower-pte-ltd-agement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Inter Island Manpower Pte Ltd Vacancies Chef Management Trainee" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/chef-management-traine-inter-island-manpower-pte-ltd-agement</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/chef-management-traine-inter-island-manpower-pte-ltd-agement/">&lt;p&gt;Inter Island Manpower Pte Ltd is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Chef Management Trainee&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Job Description&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Job Requirements:-&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prepare food items for customers as requested, including special requests, in a timely and&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;consistent manner&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Determine food and supply needs based on rotating menus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inspect food products and supplies as needed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure work environment and stations are clean and sanitized&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Check food before it is served to customers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Control and minimize waste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comply with outlined safety regulations and procedures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Job Responsibilities:-&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good work ethics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Willing to learn &amp;amp; pick up new skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good communication &amp;amp; interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Warm &amp;amp; cheerful personality&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Team player &amp;amp; able to motivate fellow staff&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work well under pressure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Candidate must possess at least a Bachelor's Degree in Food &amp;amp; Beverage Services Management, Hospitality/Tourism/Hotel Management, Culinary Artsor equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;At least 2 year(s) of working experience in the related field is required for this position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Preferably Junior Executives specializing in Food/Beverage/Restaurant Service, Hotel Management/Tourism Services, Culinary Arts or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Full-Time position(s) available.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Registration Number : R1223237&lt;br /&gt;INTER ISLAND MANPOWER PTE LTD&lt;br /&gt;(Co Reg: 200810144N / EA License: 08C3257)&lt;br /&gt;Please send your updated resume by clicking &quot;&lt;strong&gt;Apply&lt;/strong&gt;&quot;. Only shortlisted candidates will be notified.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Welcome to the &lt;strong&gt;Inter Island Group&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are a full-service employment expert specialising in the complete range of staffing services within and beyond the shores of Singapore. From foreign worker recruitment to permanent placement and executive search, our single-minded objective is to solve your employment needs professionally, speedily and effectively.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We ride on our operating philosophies of &amp;#8220;Warmth, Integrity, Responsibility and Professionalism&amp;#8221; &amp;#8211; the cornerstones of our services &amp;#8211; we are relentless in our pursuit of the ultimate customer experience, from pre to post recruitment. Our dedication lies not just in meeting your expectations, but in exceeding them; so as to make the stressful process of staffing easier, hassle-free and hopefully, enjoyable.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our team of consultants are selected from some of the finest in various industries, intensively trained to embrace our operating philosophies. Workshops are conducted regularly to update and educate our consultants in the latest industry trends and knowledge to ensure delivery of real results to companies and individuals who have come to count on us for your recruitment needs.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Benefiting from the far-reaching footprint of the Inter Island Group, we are further supported by a robust network of recruitment partners and branches globally in Taiwan, China, Malaysia, Macau and Vietnam.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Together, our inherent workforce and established partners work closely and meticulously to manage the entire recruitment process; from pursuing, matching, short-listing, analysing, screening, to finally determining the right candidates with the right skill sets and attitudes. The result: a mutually-benefiting scenario for our clients and the talents. We aim to deliver exceptional services!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Inter Island Manpower Pte Ltd EA License: 08C3527&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Singapore. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jobstreet.com.my/en/job/chef-management-trainee-8210940/origin/sg?jobId=jobstreet-sg-job-8210940&amp;amp;sectionRank=11&amp;amp;token=0~8ba97bb8-9c04-4470-885f-a5f9cdde3f6e&amp;amp;fr=SRP%20View%20In%20New%20Ta&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Singapore" /><summary type="html">Inter Island Manpower Pte Ltd is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Chef Management Trainee which positioned at Singapore</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott International Vacancies Chef de Partie</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/chef-de-partie-mariot-international-2032736/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott International Vacancies Chef de Partie" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/chef-de-partie-mariot-international-2032736</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/chef-de-partie-mariot-international-2032736/">&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Chef de Partie&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Job Description :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category&lt;/b&gt; Food and Beverage &amp;amp; Culinary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt; Courtyard Penang, 218D Jalan Macalister, George Town, Penang, Malaysia, Malaysia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brand&lt;/b&gt; Courtyard by Marriott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt; Full-time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relocation&lt;/b&gt; No&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Type&lt;/b&gt; Non-Management/Hourly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Your Journey With Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With more than 330 managed locations in more than 20 countries Courtyard by Marriott offers a refreshing environment that helps guests stay connected and balanced. Working at Courtyard, you'll ensure guests have a smooth, productive stay that meets their personal and business needs. Find Your World&amp;#8482; at Courtyard by Marriott.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prepare special meals or substitute items. Regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, and roasters. Pull food from freezer storage to thaw in the refrigerator. Ensure proper portion, arrangement, and food garnish. Maintain food logs. Monitor the quality and quantity of food that is prepared. Communicate assistance needed during busy periods. Inform Chef of excess food items for use in daily specials. Inform Food &amp;amp; Beverage service staff of menu specials and out of stock menu items. Ensure the quality of the food items. Prepare and cook food according to recipes, quality standards, presentation standards, and food preparation checklist. Prepare cold foods.&lt;br /&gt;Assist management in hiring, training, scheduling, evaluating, counseling, disciplining, and motivating and coaching employees; serve as a role model. Follow all company and safety and security policies and procedures; report maintenance needs, accidents, injuries, and unsafe work conditions to manager; complete safety training and certifications. Ensure uniform and personal appearance are clean and professional; maintain confidentiality of proprietary information; protect company assets. Anticipate and address guests&amp;#8217; service needs. Speak with others using clear and professional language. Develop and maintain positive working relationships with others; support team to reach common goals; listen and respond appropriately to the concerns of other employees. Ensure adherence to quality expectations and standards. Stand, sit, or walk for an extended period of time. Reach overhead and below the knees, including bending, twisting, pulling, and stooping. Move, lift, carry, push, pull, and place objects weighing less than or equal to 25 pounds without assistance. Perform other reasonable job duties as requested by Supervisors.&lt;i&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture. Marriott International does not discriminate on the basis of disability, veteran status or any other basis protected under federal, state or local laws.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Marriott International&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Penang , Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=2032736&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Penang" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Marriott International is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Chef de Partie which positioned at Penang , Malaysia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott International Vacancies Chef de Partie</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/chef-de-partie-mariot-international-2031214/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott International Vacancies Chef de Partie" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/chef-de-partie-mariot-international-2031214</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/chef-de-partie-mariot-international-2031214/">&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Chef de Partie&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Job Description :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category&lt;/b&gt; Food and Beverage &amp;amp; Culinary&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt; The Westin Desaru Coast Resort, Jalan Pantai 3, Desaru Coast, Bandar Penawar, Desaru, Malaysia, Malaysia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brand&lt;/b&gt; Westin Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt; Full-time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relocation&lt;/b&gt; No&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Type&lt;/b&gt; Non-Management/Hourly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Your Journey With Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Westin, we are committed to empowering the well-being of our guests by providing a refreshing environment, thoughtful amenities, and revitalizing programming to help ensure that they leave feeling better than when they arrived. We recognize that travel can be disruptive to our guests&amp;#8217; well-being, and we&amp;#8217;re energized to assist as partners in helping them maintain control and soaring above it all while on the road. Everything we do is designed to help guests be at their best, and they appreciate our supportive attitude, anticipatory service and extensive knowledge on how to best assist them throughout their stay. We are looking for dynamic people who are excited to join the team and ready to jump into any situation to give a helping hand. If you&amp;#8217;re someone who has is positive, adaptable and intuitive, and has a genuine interest in the well-being of others around you, we invite you to discover how at Westin, together we can rise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prepare special meals or substitute items. Regulate temperature of ovens, broilers, grills, and roasters. Pull food from freezer storage to thaw in the refrigerator. Ensure proper portion, arrangement, and food garnish. Maintain food logs. Monitor the quality and quantity of food that is prepared. Communicate assistance needed during busy periods. Inform Chef of excess food items for use in daily specials. Inform F&amp;amp;B service staff of 86'ed items and available menu specials. Ensure the quality of the food items. Prepare and cook food according to recipes, quality standards, presentation standards, and food preparation checklist. Prepare cold foods. Assist management in hiring, training, scheduling, evaluating, counseling, disciplining, and motivating and coaching employees; serve as a role model.&lt;br /&gt;Follow all company and safety and security policies and procedures; report maintenance needs, accidents, injuries, and unsafe work conditions to manager; complete safety training and certifications. Ensure uniform and personal appearance are clean and professional; maintain confidentiality of proprietary information; protect company assets. Anticipate and address guests service needs. Speak with others using clear and professional language. Develop and maintain positive working relationships with others; support team to reach common goals; listen and respond appropriately to the concerns of other employees. Ensure adherence to quality expectations and standards. Stand, sit, or walk for an extended period of time. Reach overhead and below the knees, including bending, twisting, pulling, and stooping. Move, lift, carry, push, pull, and place objects weighing less than or equal to 25 pounds without assistance. Perform other reasonable job duties as requested by Supervisors. &lt;i&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture. Marriott International does not discriminate on the basis of disability, veteran status or any other basis protected under federal, state or local laws.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Marriott International&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=2031214&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Marriott International is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Chef de Partie which positioned at Malaysia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hyatt Vacancies Bartender</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/bartender-hyat-190501/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hyatt Vacancies Bartender" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/bartender-hyat-190501</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/bartender-hyat-190501/">&lt;p&gt;Hyatt is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Bartender&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Summary :&lt;br /&gt;At Hyatt, we believe our guests select Hyatt because of our caring and attentive associates who are focused on providing efficient service and meaningful experiences.&amp;#160; Bartenders are responsible for providing libations and offering customized recommendations.&amp;#160; The right person should be familiar with the latest in mixology, bar equipment, and sanitation standards, with a focus on maintaining an attractive bar.&amp;#160; This position offers opportunity for casual conversation, creativity and allows for building on ones style and previous bartending experiences.&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&lt;br /&gt;Qualifications :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A true desire to satisfy the needs of others in a fast paced environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refined verbal communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must have physical stamina to lift moderate amounts of weight.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Hyatt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Kuala Lumpur , Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=1990501&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Kuala Lumpur" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Hyatt is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Bartender which positioned at Kuala Lumpur , Malaysia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott International Vacancies B&amp;amp;F Sales Manager 饮食销售</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/b-f-sales-manager-mariot-international-1960832/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott International Vacancies B&amp;amp;F Sales Manager 饮食销售" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/b-f-sales-manager-mariot-international-1960832</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/b-f-sales-manager-mariot-international-1960832/">&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;B&amp;amp;F Sales Manager 饮食销售&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Job Description :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category&lt;/b&gt; Sales and Marketing&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt; JW Marriott Hotel Kuala Lumpur, 183 Jalan Bukit Bintang, Kuala Lumpur, Wilayah Persekutuan, Malaysia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brand&lt;/b&gt; Marriott Hotels Resorts /JW Marriott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt; Full-time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relocation&lt;/b&gt; No&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Type&lt;/b&gt; Non-Management/Hourly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Your Journey With Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Boldly coloring outside the lines of luxury, W turns the traditional notion of the extravagant hotel on its head. Our irreverent attitude and taste for excess redefine revelry for the modern jet set. Our guests have a lust for a life less ordinary that drives them to demand more, experience it all, and hit repeat.&lt;br /&gt;We share our guests&amp;#8217; passions, providing insider access to what&amp;#8217;s new and what&amp;#8217;s next. Moderation is not in our vocabulary and we know that lust for life demands more, not less. W guests soak it in and live each day with a mantra: Detox.Retox.Repeat. If you&amp;#8217;re ready to create the energetic W scene that is magnetic to everyday disruptors around the world, then we invite you to explore a career with W Hotels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact appropriate individual or department (e.g., Sales, Data Administration, Accounting) as necessary to resolve guest calls, requests, or problems. Use sales techniques that maximize revenue while maintaining existing guest loyalty to Marriott, including up-selling. Determine and give complimentaries to guests as gifts for their patronage (e.g., rewards points, show tickets, gift certificates). Promote awareness of brand image internally and externally. Process requests for redeeming Marriott Rewards points. Process all reservation requests, changes, and cancellations received by phone, fax, or mail. Enter Marriott Rewards information into appropriate software when taking guest reservations. Answer, record, and process all guest calls, requests, questions, or concerns. Perform general office duties to support Sales &amp;amp; Marketing (e.g., filing, sending emails, typing, faxing). Assist management in training and motivating employees; serve as a role model.&lt;br /&gt;Follow all company policies and procedures; ensure uniform and personal appearance are clean and professional; maintain confidentiality of proprietary information; protect company assets. Welcome and acknowledge all guests according to company standards; anticipate and address guests service needs; thank guests with genuine appreciation. Speak with others using clear and professional language; prepare and review written documents accurately and completely; answer telephones using appropriate etiquette. Develop and maintain positive working relationships with others; support team to reach common goals; listen and respond appropriately to the concerns of other employees. Monitor the performance of others to ensure adherence to quality expectations and standards. Read and visually verify information in a variety of formats. Move, lift, carry, push, pull, and place objects weighing less than or equal to 10 pounds without assistance. Perform other reasonable job duties as requested by Supervisors.&lt;i&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture. Marriott International does not discriminate on the basis of disability, veteran status or any other basis protected under federal, state or local laws.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Marriott International&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Kuala Lumpur , Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=1960832&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Kuala Lumpur" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Marriott International is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the B&amp;F Sales Manager 饮食销售 which positioned at Kuala Lumpur , Malaysia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott International Vacancies Assistant Manager, Concierge / Service Express</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/asistant-manager-concierge-service-expres-mariot-international-198579/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott International Vacancies Assistant Manager, Concierge / Service Express" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/asistant-manager-concierge-service-expres-mariot-international-198579</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/asistant-manager-concierge-service-expres-mariot-international-198579/">&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Assistant Manager, Concierge / Service Express&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Job Description :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category&lt;/b&gt; Rooms and Guest Services Operations&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt; The Westin Langkawi Resort &amp;amp; Spa, Jalan Pantai Dato, Langkawi, Malaysia, Malaysia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brand&lt;/b&gt; Westin Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt; Full-time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relocation&lt;/b&gt; No&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Type&lt;/b&gt; Management&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Your Journey With Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Westin, we are committed to empowering the well-being of our guests by providing a refreshing environment, thoughtful amenities, and revitalizing programming to help ensure that they leave feeling better than when they arrived. We recognize that travel can be disruptive to our guests&amp;#8217; well-being, and we&amp;#8217;re energized to assist as partners in helping them maintain control and soaring above it all while on the road. Everything we do is designed to help guests be at their best, and they appreciate our supportive attitude, anticipatory service and extensive knowledge on how to best assist them throughout their stay. We are looking for dynamic people who are excited to join the team and ready to jump into any situation to give a helping hand. If you&amp;#8217;re someone who has is positive, adaptable and intuitive, and has a genuine interest in the well-being of others around you, we invite you to discover how at Westin, together we can rise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;JOB SUMMARY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Responsible for supporting all aspects of Concierge functions in accordance with hotel standards. Maintains a concierge service and management philosophy that serves as a guide to respective staff. Assists in developing and maintaining the acknowledgment and service of all guests visiting the location. Supports management to ensure all departments are aware of all guests&amp;#8217; needs and information prior to arrival that will lead to a unique, memorable and personal stay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANDIDATE PROFILE &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Education and Experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; High school diploma or GED; 2 years experience in the guest services, front desk, or related professional area.&lt;br /&gt;OR&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; 2-year degree from an accredited university in Hotel and Restaurant Management, Hospitality, Business Administration or related major; no prior work experience required&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CORE WORK ACTIVITIES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maintaining Concierge Goals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Coordinates day-to-day operations, ensuring the quality, standards and meeting the expectations of the customers on a daily basis.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Develops specific goals and plans to prioritize, organize, and accomplish work.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Supports concierge team to keep them focused on the critical components of operations to drive guest satisfaction and the desired financial results.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Understands the impact of department&amp;#8217;s operations on the overall property financial goals and objectives and manages to achieve or exceed goals.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Supports the establishment of an effective database to be used by all team members for restaurant and local attractions.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Establishes relationships with local attractions, restaurants and other businesses to enhance guests&amp;#8217; experiences.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides recommendations and arranges services for guests as requested (e.g., car rental, airline and train tickets, office services, beauty and barber services, baby sitting, repairs, shopping).&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Maintains awareness of cultural differences needed to meet guest's specific needs and requirements.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides check-in and check-out services and handles reservations when needed.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Maintains knowledge of rooms and their locations, services and facilities of the hotel.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Ensures repeat and VIP guests are receiving appropriate service and ensures their requests are carried out.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Responds to emergency situations using appropriate procedures.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Maintains awareness of daily operations and events at the hotel.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Maintains knowledge of daily house-count, arrivals/departures, VIPs, scheduled in-house group names, background, activities, locations, and times as well as special requests/arrangements&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides warm welcome and anticipation of guest needs throughout their stay.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Encourages and building mutual trust, respect, and cooperation among team members.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Serving as a role model to demonstrate appropriate behaviors.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Establishes and maintains open, collaborative relationships with employees and ensures employees do the same within the team.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Ensures concierge team effectively handles guest requests and adheres to all hotel policies, procedures and standards while striving towards total guest satisfaction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ensuring Exceptional Customer Service &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Assists in ensuring the concierge team provides services that are above and beyond for customer satisfaction and retention.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Improves service by assisting individuals to understand guest needs, providing guidance, feedback, and individual coaching when needed.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Responds to and handles guest problems and complaints.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Sets a positive example for guest relations.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Interacts with customers to obtain feedback on quality of product, service levels and overall satisfaction.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Supports employees understanding of customer service expectations and parameters.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Interacts with guests to obtain feedback on product quality and service levels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Additional Responsibilities &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides information to supervisors and co-workers by telephone, in written form, e-mail, or in person.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Analyzes information and evaluates results to choose the best solution and solve problems.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Informs and/or updates the executives and the peers on relevant information in a timely manner.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Participates in departmental meetings and continually communicates a clear and consistent message regarding the front of house goals to produce desired results.&lt;i&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture. Marriott International does not discriminate on the basis of disability, veteran status or any other basis protected under federal, state or local laws.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Marriott International&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=1985799&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Marriott International is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Assistant Manager, Concierge / Service Express which positioned at Malaysia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott International Vacancies Assistant Accounts Manager</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/asistant-acounts-manager-mariot-international-1985798/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott International Vacancies Assistant Accounts Manager" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/asistant-acounts-manager-mariot-international-1985798</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/asistant-acounts-manager-mariot-international-1985798/">&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Assistant Accounts Manager&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Job Description :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category&lt;/b&gt; Finance and Accounting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt; Miri Marriott Resort &amp;amp; Spa, Jalan Temenggong Datuk Oyong Lawai, Miri, Sarawak, Malaysia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brand&lt;/b&gt; Marriott Hotels Resorts /JW Marriott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt; Full-time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Type&lt;/b&gt; Non-Management/Hourly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Your Journey With Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marriott International portfolio of brands includes both JW Marriott and Marriott Hotels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Marriott Hotels&lt;/b&gt;, Marriott International&amp;#8217;s flagship brand with more than 500 global locations, is advancing the art of hosting so that our guests can travel brilliantly. As a host with Marriott Hotels, you will help keep this promise by delivering premium choices, sophisticated style, and well-crafted details. With your skills and imagination, together we will innovate and reinvent the future of travel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;JW Marriott &lt;/b&gt;is part of Marriott International's luxury portfolio and consists of more than 80 beautiful properties in gateway cities and distinctive resort locations around the world. JW believes our associates come first. Because if you&amp;#8217;re happy, our guests will be happy. It&amp;#8217;s as simple as that. Our hotels offer a work experience unlike any other, where you&amp;#8217;ll be part of a community and enjoy a true camaraderie with a diverse group of co-workers. JW creates opportunities for training, development, recognition and most importantly, a place where you can really pursue your passions in a luxury environment. Treating guests exceptionally starts with the way we take care of our associates. That&amp;#8217;s The JW Treatment&amp;#8482;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check figures, postings, and documents for accuracy. Organize, secure, and maintain all files, records, cash and cash equivalents in accordance with policies and procedures. Record, store, access, and/or analyze computerized financial information. Classify, code, and summarize numerical and financial data to compile and keep financial records, using journals, ledgers, and/or computers. Prepare, maintain, audit, and distribute statistical, financial, accounting, auditing, or payroll reports and tables. Complete period-end closing procedures and reports as specified. Prepare, review, reconcile, and issue bills, invoices, and account statements according to company procedures. Follow-up and resolve past due accounts and vendor invoices until payment in full is received or resolved. Coordinate tasks and work with other departments; serve as a departmental role model or mentor; assign and ensure work tasks are completed on time and that they meet appropriate quality standards. Report work related accidents, or other injuries immediately upon occurrence to manager/supervisor.&lt;br /&gt;Follow all company policies and procedures; ensure uniform and personal appearance are clean and professional; maintain confidentiality of proprietary information; protect company assets. Speak with others using clear and professional language; prepare and review written documents accurately and completely; answer telephones using appropriate etiquette. Develop and maintain positive working relationships with others; support team to reach common goals; listen and respond appropriately to the concerns of other employees. Move, lift, carry, push, pull, and place objects weighing less than or equal to 10 pounds without assistance. Perform other reasonable job duties as requested by Supervisors.&lt;i&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture. Marriott International does not discriminate on the basis of disability, veteran status or any other basis protected under federal, state or local laws.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Marriott International&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=1985798&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Marriott International is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Assistant Accounts Manager which positioned at Malaysia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott International Vacancies Accounting Supervisor</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/acounting-supervisor-mariot-international-2032735/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott International Vacancies Accounting Supervisor" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/acounting-supervisor-mariot-international-2032735</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/acounting-supervisor-mariot-international-2032735/">&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Accounting Supervisor&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Job Description :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category&lt;/b&gt; Finance and Accounting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt; JW Marriott Hotel Kuala Lumpur, 183 Jalan Bukit Bintang, Kuala Lumpur, Wilayah Persekutuan, Malaysia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brand&lt;/b&gt; Marriott Hotels Resorts /JW Marriott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt; Full-time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Type&lt;/b&gt; Non-Management/Hourly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Your Journey With Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marriott International portfolio of brands includes both JW Marriott and Marriott Hotels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Marriott Hotels&lt;/b&gt;, Marriott International&amp;#8217;s flagship brand with more than 500 global locations, is advancing the art of hosting so that our guests can travel brilliantly. As a host with Marriott Hotels, you will help keep this promise by delivering premium choices, sophisticated style, and well-crafted details. With your skills and imagination, together we will innovate and reinvent the future of travel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;JW Marriott &lt;/b&gt;is part of Marriott International's luxury portfolio and consists of more than 80 beautiful properties in gateway cities and distinctive resort locations around the world. JW believes our associates come first. Because if you&amp;#8217;re happy, our guests will be happy. It&amp;#8217;s as simple as that. Our hotels offer a work experience unlike any other, where you&amp;#8217;ll be part of a community and enjoy a true camaraderie with a diverse group of co-workers. JW creates opportunities for training, development, recognition and most importantly, a place where you can really pursue your passions in a luxury environment. Treating guests exceptionally starts with the way we take care of our associates. That&amp;#8217;s The JW Treatment&amp;#8482;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check figures, postings, and documents for accuracy. Organize, secure, and maintain all files, records, cash and cash equivalents in accordance with policies and procedures. Record, store, access, and/or analyze computerized financial information. Classify, code, and summarize numerical and financial data to compile and keep financial records, using journals, ledgers, and/or computers. Prepare, maintain, audit, and distribute statistical, financial, accounting, auditing, or payroll reports and tables. Complete period-end closing procedures and reports as specified. Prepare, review, reconcile, and issue bills, invoices, and account statements according to company procedures. Follow-up and resolve past due accounts and vendor invoices until payment in full is received or resolved. Coordinate tasks and work with other departments; serve as a departmental role model or mentor; assign and ensure work tasks are completed on time and that they meet appropriate quality standards. Report work related accidents, or other injuries immediately upon occurrence to manager/supervisor.&lt;br /&gt;Follow all company policies and procedures; ensure uniform and personal appearance are clean and professional; maintain confidentiality of proprietary information; protect company assets. Speak with others using clear and professional language; prepare and review written documents accurately and completely; answer telephones using appropriate etiquette. Develop and maintain positive working relationships with others; support team to reach common goals; listen and respond appropriately to the concerns of other employees. Move, lift, carry, push, pull, and place objects weighing less than or equal to 10 pounds without assistance. Perform other reasonable job duties as requested by Supervisors.&lt;i&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture. Marriott International does not discriminate on the basis of disability, veteran status or any other basis protected under federal, state or local laws.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Marriott International&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Kuala Lumpur , Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=2032735&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Kuala Lumpur" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Marriott International is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Accounting Supervisor which positioned at Kuala Lumpur , Malaysia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">TDOX Clinic Vacancies Operation Manager</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/operation-manager-tdox-clinic-428592/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TDOX Clinic Vacancies Operation Manager" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/operation-manager-tdox-clinic-428592</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/operation-manager-tdox-clinic-428592/">&lt;p&gt;TDOX Clinic is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Operation Manager&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Job Description&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;To communicate management&amp;#8217;s and medical director&amp;#8217;s objective to the team and to ensure the efforts of the team are focused and able to come up with good service strategy and KPI&amp;#8217;s (Key Performance Indicator) to improve quality of service for continuous improvement.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To propose training for staff as regards to quality customer service &amp;amp; ensure the entire team&amp;#160;reach to the standard set by the Company and to develop a relationship of trust with clients through consistent communication and reliably carrying out responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Update Clients on current facilities and new services provided by the center and able to solve client&amp;#8217;s problems and being able to track and monitor their feedback efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To come up with Standard Operating Procedures (SOP&amp;#8217;s) for Client Service and Operation Department.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To ensure all reports are submitted before deadlines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Increase the effectiveness and efficiency of Client Service and Operation Team through improvements to each function as well as coordination and communication between functions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contribute to short and long-term organizational planning and strategy as a member of the management team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coordinate, supervise, manage and monitor the workings of client service and operation team in the organization.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A medical tourism centre licensed by Malaysia Ministry of Health. The luxury of world class facilities that promotes top-notch medical aesthetics and regenerative medicine delivering customized, personalized &amp;amp; luxury experience towards youth, vitality and longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Kuala Lumpur. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jobstreet.com.my/en/job/operation-manager-4428592?jobId=jobstreet-my-job-4428592&amp;amp;sectionRank=2&amp;amp;token=0~8ba97bb8-9c04-4470-885f-a5f9cdde3f6e&amp;amp;fr=SRP%20View%20In%20New%20Ta&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Kuala Lumpur" /><summary type="html">TDOX Clinic is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Operation Manager which positioned at Kuala Lumpur</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott International Vacancies Purchasing Executive</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/purchasing-executive-mariot-international-2031213/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott International Vacancies Purchasing Executive" /><published>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-21T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/purchasing-executive-mariot-international-2031213</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/purchasing-executive-mariot-international-2031213/">&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Purchasing Executive&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Job Description :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category&lt;/b&gt; Procurement, Purchasing, and Quality Assurance&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt; The St. Regis Kuala Lumpur, Jalan Stesen Sentral &amp;amp; Jalan Travers, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, Malaysia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brand&lt;/b&gt; St. Regis Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt; Full-time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relocation&lt;/b&gt; No&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Type&lt;/b&gt; Non-Management/Hourly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Your Journey With Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The St. Regis brand first established luxury hospitality more than 110 years ago, with the opening of the St. Regis New York. From the moment John Jacob Astor IV opened the doors of his Beaux-Arts masterpiece on New York&amp;#8217;s Fifth Avenue, St. Regis has stood as a symbol of uncompromising elegance and bespoke service. Today, with more than 40 of the best addresses around the world, St. Regis is a place where trends are born, boundaries are broken and guests can simply live exquisite. We invite you to explore careers at St. Regis.&lt;br /&gt;Print and organize various necessary documents, summarize relevant information, and distribute information to appropriate employees. Maintain up-to-date knowledge of company food safety programs, as well as all local, state, and federal regulations. Adhere to food safety and handling policies and procedures across all food-related areas. Maintain clear and organized records to ensure all reports and invoices are filed and stored properly. Calculate figures for food inventories, orders, and costs. Conduct inventory audits to determine inventory levels and needs. Notify manager/supervisor of low stock levels. Troubleshoot vendor delivery issues and oversee return process. Verify and track received inventory. Reconcile shipping invoices and receiving reports. Receive, unload, and process deliveries. Monitor PAR levels for all food items to ensure proper levels. Refuse acceptance of damaged, unacceptable, or incorrect items. Assist management in training, scheduling, counseling, disciplining, and motivating and coaching employees; serve as a role model. Ensure adherence to quality expectations and standards. Report accidents, injuries, and unsafe work conditions to manager; complete safety training and certifications.&lt;br /&gt;Follow all company and safety and security policies and procedures; report any maintenance problems, safety hazards, accidents, or injuries; complete safety training and certifications. Ensure uniform and personal appearance are clean and professional. Maintain confidentiality of proprietary information; protect company assets. Support all co-workers and treat them with dignity and respect. Support team to reach common goals. Comply with quality assurance expectations and standards. Move, lift, carry, push, pull, and place objects weighing less than or equal to 50 pounds without assistance. Stand, sit, or walk for an extended period of time or for an entire work shift. Read and visually verify information in a variety of formats (e. g., small print). Grasp, turn, and manipulate objects of varying and weight, requiring fine motor skills and hand-eye coordination. Move through narrow, confined, or elevated spaces. Move over sloping, uneven, or slippery surfaces and steps. Move up and down stairs and/or service ramps. Listen and respond appropriately to the concerns of other employees. Speak with others using clear and professional language. Perform other reasonable job duties as requested by Supervisors.&lt;i&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture. Marriott International does not discriminate on the basis of disability, veteran status or any other basis protected under federal, state or local laws.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Marriott International&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Kuala Lumpur , Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=2031213&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Kuala Lumpur" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Marriott International is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Purchasing Executive which positioned at Kuala Lumpur , Malaysia</summary></entry></feed>