<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-25T19:45:11+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html"> </title><subtitle>Jawatan Kosong Hotel. Malaysia hotel jobs 2020 / 2021</subtitle><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">Only World Group Vacancies Indoor Themepark Crew - 1 year contract</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/indor-themepark-crew-1-year-contract-only-world-group-429790/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Only World Group Vacancies Indoor Themepark Crew - 1 year contract" /><published>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/indor-themepark-crew-1-year-contract-only-world-group-429790</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/indor-themepark-crew-1-year-contract-only-world-group-429790/">&lt;p&gt;Only World Group is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Indoor Themepark Crew - 1 year contract&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Job Description&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that due to CMCO regulations, the park is now closed. All shortlisted candidates start date will be determined subjected by MKN SOPs and regulations on opening.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Be a part of our fun-filled attraction; indoor playground featuring fun slides, crawling tunnels, climbing structures, ball pit and many more!&amp;#160; We also offer arts and crafts activity for patrons 3- 7years old. We need those who are creative, outgoing individuals who are comfortable with children to make this activities work&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; To organize and lead children activities involving simple arts and crafts projects&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; To encourage creativity and curiosity of children&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; To plan, design and execute arts and craft activities&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; To monitor and ensure safety of children under your care during the crafts activities&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; Constantly help the management to improve processes and give new idea&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; To keep a watchful eye on children and ensure they are safe at all times.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; To constantly check outlet assets such as slides, swings, etc are in tip top condition. In any case of damage to assets, you are to report to maintenance at the soonest.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; To assist in the preparation of any events organized at outlet, which includes setup of booths, props preparation and food &amp;amp; beverage preparation.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; To assist with administration tasks&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;#8226; Ensure that play area and surrounding areas are cleaned thoroughly.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Staff benefits&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overtime&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staff meal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Annual leave&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medical claims&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;EPF,SOCSO contribution&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;Requirement&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Experience working with children is highly encouraged to apply&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Creative, patient, outgoing and pleasant personality&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Available to work &lt;strong&gt;six days&lt;/strong&gt; a week (of days on Weekdays) and on shift hours within park opening hour&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226;Must be willing to work on&lt;strong&gt; weekends and Public Holidays&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
		If you crave new challenges that will keep your enthusiasm at its peak. If you have the mind to inspire others and be inspired, and if you simply enjoy a career that stimulates your excitement, you have come to the right place. ONLY WORLD GROUP owns and operates Malaysia&amp;#8217;s largest water theme park chain, F&amp;amp;B outlets, various family entertainment attractions and theme park development. We have built an empire of companies that operates in line with our core values &amp;#8211; Fun, Food and Good Living. In line with our RAPID expansion, we invite dynamic and ambitious individuals to join us IMMEDIATELY !&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;History&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
		In 1973, ONLY WORLD GROUP started out as an office equipment and related services provider under the name of World Equipment Sdn Bhd. Over the years, it grew to become a supplier of sophisticated theme park equipments and rides, earning the reputation as the region's top recreational equipment supplier and professional theme park consultant and builder. The OWG business now includes family restaurants, spas, amusement / theme parks and leisure attractions at popular resorts. Growing from strength to strength, the Group is bound to set new trends in the amusement and themeparks, food and beverages, attractions and leisure sectors in Malaysia and around the world.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Product &amp;amp; Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
		Inspired by the strong and silent demeanour of the horse,&amp;#160;Only World Group&amp;#160;has emerged from its humble beginnings to becoming Malaysia&amp;#8217;s leading amusement and recreation theme park developer. It has been working behind the scenes, silently, in bringing people together and creating fond memories until present. The wealth of the Group&amp;#8217;s experience has gained them recognition as one of the region&amp;#8217;s esteemed theme park consultant whose expertise include designing, building and managing operation of parks. Its prowess in this industry has proven with turnkey and contracted projects Resorts World Genting, Universal Studios Singapore, Mines Wonderland, Desa WaterPark and Sunway Lagoon. As the Group embraces the philosophy of &amp;#8220;Fun,&amp;#160;Food&amp;#160;and&amp;#160;Good Living&amp;#8221;, it also make strides in operating and managing F&amp;amp;B and leisure related brands, found in popular resorts and shopping malls. The Group ventures into good living by providing outlets to relax the body and revitalise the mind namely spas and other related activities. As the future beholds,&amp;#160;Only World Group&amp;#160;will continue to run ahead in affirming our position of being Only the Best in what we do. With our experience, coupled with forward thinking leaders, we will implement the best business strategy and system in exploring new horizons to create more sparks that will excite the world in terms of &amp;#8220;Fun,&amp;#160;Food and&amp;#160;Good Living&amp;#8221;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Selangor. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jobstreet.com.my/en/job/indoor-themepark-crew-1-year-contract-4429790?jobId=jobstreet-my-job-4429790&amp;amp;sectionRank=6&amp;amp;token=0~bb56468e-9348-436c-851c-de61076b662b&amp;amp;fr=SRP%20View%20In%20New%20Ta&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Selangor" /><summary type="html">Only World Group is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Indoor Themepark Crew - 1 year contract which positioned at Selangor</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">One &amp;amp; Only Desaru Coast Vacancies Assistant Manager, Guest Service</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/asistant-manager-guest-service-one-only-desaru-coast-43086/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="One &amp;amp; Only Desaru Coast Vacancies Assistant Manager, Guest Service" /><published>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/asistant-manager-guest-service-one-only-desaru-coast-43086</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/asistant-manager-guest-service-one-only-desaru-coast-43086/">&lt;p&gt;One &amp;amp; Only Desaru Coast is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Assistant Manager, Guest Service&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Job Description&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JOB SUMMARY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A guest services manager at a hotel is responsible for ensuring that all aspects of a customer's stay at their hotel is not only satisfactory but exceeds their expectations. The guest services manager oversees booking processes and handles the reservation and scheduling of offered amenities (like spa treatments) and is also responsible for ensuring efficient handling of room service orders. They generally work with other managers in departments such as housekeeping to ensure that all hotel guests have enjoyable and memorable experiences.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure and provide flawless, upscale, professional, and high-class guest service experiences.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analyze customer feedback and provide strategic direction to continuously improve overall rating.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Respond to guests needs and anticipate their unstated ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coordinate and manage communication between guests and staff and follow up to ensure complete service recovery.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oversee and managing butler services as and when required.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oversee and coordinate all arrivals and departures of special guests.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with Valet complete all room moves, ensuring all moves are done on time with less disruption and guests are comfortably accommodated.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JOB REQUIREMENT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Candidate must possess at least Diploma/Advanced/Higher/Graduate Diploma in Hospitality/Tourism/Hotel Management or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Able to communicate and written fluently in English and Bahasa Malaysia.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pleasant personality and self-grooming are essentials.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;At least 3&amp;#160;Years of working experience in a similar role with a luxury resort/hotel.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Night Audit working experience would be carry added advantages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Able to work in a fast-paced environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Applicable for Citizen of Malaysia and/or valid Permanent Residents of Malaysia only.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&quot;Kerzner International Holdings Limited (&amp;#8220;Kerzner&amp;#8221;), the owner of the ultra-luxury One&amp;amp;Only Resorts and iconic Atlantis Resort &amp;amp; Residences brands worldwide is pleased to announce the introduction of One&amp;amp;Only Desaru Coast in Malaysia.&amp;#160;&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;A 128-acre beachfront development, this ultimate bespoke lifestyle experience will include 42 suites, 2 luxury suites and an exclusive 4-bedroom villa, as well as approximately 50 One&amp;amp;Only Private Homes available for purchase. This will be the first One&amp;amp;Only in Malaysia as part of the expanding One&amp;amp;Only collection, as the brand continues to grow and develop internationally. Kerzner manages a portfolio of globally renowned, landmark destination resorts, luxury hotels and residences and innovative entertainment experiences.&quot;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Johor - Others. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jobstreet.com.my/en/job/assistant-manager-guest-service-4430086?jobId=jobstreet-my-job-4430086&amp;amp;sectionRank=4&amp;amp;token=0~bb56468e-9348-436c-851c-de61076b662b&amp;amp;fr=SRP%20View%20In%20New%20Ta&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Johor - Others" /><summary type="html">One &amp; Only Desaru Coast is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Assistant Manager, Guest Service which positioned at Johor - Others</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Grant Hyatt Kuala Lumpur Hotel Vacancies - Bartender and Pastry Chef</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/grant-hyatt-kl-bartender-pastry-chef/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grant Hyatt Kuala Lumpur Hotel Vacancies - Bartender and Pastry Chef" /><published>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/grant-hyatt-kl-bartender-pastry-chef</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/grant-hyatt-kl-bartender-pastry-chef/">&lt;p&gt;Grant Hyatt Kuala Lumpur Hotel is currently looking for suitable person to fill Bartender and Pastry Chef positions.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;vacancies&quot;&gt;Vacancies&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bartender&lt;/strong&gt;
Responsible for providing libations and offering customized recommendations. The right person should be
familiar with the latest in mixology. bar equipment and sanitation standards. with a focus on maintaining an
attractive bar. This position offers opportunity for casual conversation and creative bartending style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Atrue desire to satisfy the needs of othersin a fast paced environment.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Refined verbal communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Must have physical stamina to lift moderate amounts of weight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pastry Chef&lt;/strong&gt;
Responsible to function as the Production Manager for all pastry and bakery products. making sure that they
contribute to the overall success of outlets and banquets, in accordance with the hotel’s standards and
financial goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ideally with an apprenticeship or professional diploma in Food Production with pastry specialization or
professionally recognized diploma in Pastry Arts.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years work experience as Pastry Chef or Assistant Pastry Chef in world renowned quality large
multiple outlet operation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Creative with understanding of current pastry concepts and trends with the ability to benchmark and
develop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;benefits&quot;&gt;Benefits&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We provide the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5 Working Days&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Uniform Provision &amp;amp; Laundering&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insurance Coverage (Inciuding Dental)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Complimentary Stays Worldwide&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Career Advancement &amp;amp; Transfer Opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/2020-11/grant-hyatt-kl-bartender-pastry-chef.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Grant Hyatt KL Jobs Ad 2020!&quot; title=&quot;Grant Hyatt KL Jobs 2020&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only applicable to Malaysian citizen and permanent resident of Malaysia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
APPLY NOW at careers.hyatt.com
or
EMAIL your resume to kuagh.hr@hyatt.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Address
&lt;strong&gt;Grand Hyatt Kuala Lumpur&lt;/strong&gt;
12 Jalan Pinang, 50450, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia
Telephone +603 2182 1234&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We regret that only shortlisted candidates will be notified.
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Kuala Lumpur" /><summary type="html">Grant Hyatt Kuala Lumpur Hotel is currently looking for suitable person to fill Bartender and Pastry Chef positions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">JSK Group Of Companies Vacancies Capsule Hotel Operations Manager</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/capsule-hotel-operations-manager-jsk-group-of-companies-430831/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="JSK Group Of Companies Vacancies Capsule Hotel Operations Manager" /><published>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/capsule-hotel-operations-manager-jsk-group-of-companies-430831</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/capsule-hotel-operations-manager-jsk-group-of-companies-430831/">&lt;p&gt;JSK Group Of Companies is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Capsule Hotel Operations Manager&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Job Highlights&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;International Group of Companies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cross Industry Career Opportunities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wide Exposure Training Options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Career Level&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Manager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Qualification&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Professional Certificate, Diploma, Advanced/Higher/Graduate Diploma, Bachelor's Degree, Post Graduate Diploma, Professional Degree&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Years of Experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;5 years&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Job Type&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Full-Time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Job Specializations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hotel/Restaurant, Hotel/Tourism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Kota Kinabalu. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jobstreet.com.my/en/job/capsule-hotel-operations-manager-4430831?jobId=jobstreet-my-job-4430831&amp;amp;sectionRank=2&amp;amp;token=0~bb56468e-9348-436c-851c-de61076b662b&amp;amp;fr=SRP%20View%20In%20New%20Ta&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Kota Kinabalu" /><summary type="html">JSK Group Of Companies is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Capsule Hotel Operations Manager which positioned at Kota Kinabalu</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Best View Hotel Subang Jaya Jobs Vacancies</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/best-view-hotel-subang-jaya-jobs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Best View Hotel Subang Jaya Jobs Vacancies" /><published>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-25T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/best-view-hotel-subang-jaya-jobs</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/best-view-hotel-subang-jaya-jobs/">&lt;p&gt;Best View Hotel Subang Jaya is currently looking for few persons for these positions.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;about&quot;&gt;About&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best View Hotel Subang Jaya is located at SS15/5A road, Subang Jaya and near to popular shopping and leisure malls like Subang Parade, Summit Usj, Aeon Big, Empire Shopping Gallery, Mydin Subang Jaya, The 19 Usj City, Sunway Lagoon Theme Park etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;vacancies&quot;&gt;Vacancies&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;HOTEL SUPERVISOR&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;HOTEL RECEPTIONIST&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;HOUSEKEEPING
LOCATION : SUBANG JAYA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/2020-11/best-view-hotel-subang-jaya-jobs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Best View Hotel Subang Jaya Ad 2020!&quot; title=&quot;Best View Hotel Subang Jaya Jobs 2020&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Please contact the person-in-charge
CONTACT NUMBER : +612-322 4561
PERSON-IN-CHARGE : MS JOANNE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Address
&lt;strong&gt;Best View Hotel Subang Jaya&lt;/strong&gt;
Address: No. 141 (G, 1st &amp;amp; 2nd Floor) Jalan SS15/5A, 47500 Subang Jaya&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We regret that only shortlisted candidates will be notified.
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Selangor" /><summary type="html">Best View Hotel Subang Jaya is currently looking for few persons for these positions.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Koperasi Kakitangan Bank Rakyat Berhad Vacancies PENGURUSAN CLUBHOUSE SEKATA APARTMENT</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/pengurusan-clubhouse-sekata-apartment-koperasi-kakitangan-bank-rakyat-berhad-4251/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Koperasi Kakitangan Bank Rakyat Berhad Vacancies PENGURUSAN CLUBHOUSE SEKATA APARTMENT" /><published>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/pengurusan-clubhouse-sekata-apartment-koperasi-kakitangan-bank-rakyat-berhad-4251</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/pengurusan-clubhouse-sekata-apartment-koperasi-kakitangan-bank-rakyat-berhad-4251/">&lt;p&gt;Koperasi Kakitangan Bank Rakyat Berhad is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;PENGURUSAN CLUBHOUSE SEKATA APARTMENT&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Job Description&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Candidate must possess at least Bachelor's Degree/Post Graduate Diploma/Professional Degree in Hospitality/Tourism/Hotel Management or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Required language(s):&amp;#160;Bahasa Malaysia, English&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;At least 1&amp;#160;Year(s) of working experience in the related field is required for this position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Preferably Junior Executive specialized in Hotel Management/Tourism Services or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Berdisiplin.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Boleh menerima teguran dan arahan dengan baik.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Boleh bekerja dalam pasukan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Boleh memberi pandangan secara realistik kepada Pengurusan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Boleh bekerja dalam tekanan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mampu melaksanakan tugas seperti yang telah ditetapkan dengan baik.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Memberikan Pembiayaan kepada anggota koperasi , menjadi agen insurans kepada syarikat-syarikat insurans Takaful dan mengendalikan insurans kepada peminjam-peminjam Bank Rakyat, perkhidmatan pembersihan di cawangan-cawangan Bank Rakyat, sewaan tanah, pengurusan harian Kafeteria dan kedai di Bank Rakyat Jalan Tangsi Kuala lumpur. Pembukaan perniagaan Ar-Rahnu dibawah franchais Ar-Rahnu X'Change PJ Old Town, Ar-Rahnu X'Change Sg Besi Ar-Rahnu X'Change Taman Selaseh Ar Rahnu X'Change Hulu langat Ar Rahnu X'Change Bandar Kinrara Ar Rahnu X'Change Seremban 2 Ar rahnu X'Change Kota Kemuning &amp;amp; Ar Rahnu X'Change Dengkil.Mengembangkan perniagaan dalam bidang asuhan kanak-kanak.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Cameron Highlands. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jobstreet.com.my/en/job/pengurusan-clubhouse-sekata-apartment-4425511?jobId=jobstreet-my-job-4425511&amp;amp;sectionRank=4&amp;amp;token=0~291706cb-3b70-4dd0-a248-e83faafa4cc5&amp;amp;fr=SRP%20View%20In%20New%20Ta&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Cameron Highlands" /><summary type="html">Koperasi Kakitangan Bank Rakyat Berhad is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the PENGURUSAN CLUBHOUSE SEKATA APARTMENT which positioned at Cameron Highlands</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Koperasi Kakitangan Bank Rakyat Berhad Vacancies PENYAMBUT TETAMU CLUBHOUSE SEKATA APARTMENT</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/penyambut-tetamu-clubhouse-sekata-apartment-koperasi-kakitangan-bank-rakyat-berhad-42598/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Koperasi Kakitangan Bank Rakyat Berhad Vacancies PENYAMBUT TETAMU CLUBHOUSE SEKATA APARTMENT" /><published>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/penyambut-tetamu-clubhouse-sekata-apartment-koperasi-kakitangan-bank-rakyat-berhad-42598</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/penyambut-tetamu-clubhouse-sekata-apartment-koperasi-kakitangan-bank-rakyat-berhad-42598/">&lt;p&gt;Koperasi Kakitangan Bank Rakyat Berhad is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;PENYAMBUT TETAMU CLUBHOUSE SEKATA APARTMENT&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Job Description&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Candidate must possess at least Primary/Secondary School/SPM/&quot;O&quot; Level, Diploma/Advanced/Higher/Graduate Diploma in Hospitality/Tourism/Hotel Management or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Required language(s):&amp;#160;Bahasa Malaysia, English&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;At least 1&amp;#160;Year(s) of working experience in the related field is required for this position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Preferably Non-Executive specialized in Hotel Management/Tourism Services or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Seorang yang berdisiplin dan menepati masa.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Boleh bertugas secara &quot;multi-tasking&quot;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Boleh bertugas lebih masa (sekiranya diarahkan).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Seorang yang amanah, jujur, bertanggungjawab dan berintegriti dalam menjalankan tugas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Boleh menerima arahan dengan baik.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Berperwatakan menarik dan keterampilan kemas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Memberikan Pembiayaan kepada anggota koperasi , menjadi agen insurans kepada syarikat-syarikat insurans Takaful dan mengendalikan insurans kepada peminjam-peminjam Bank Rakyat, perkhidmatan pembersihan di cawangan-cawangan Bank Rakyat, sewaan tanah, pengurusan harian Kafeteria dan kedai di Bank Rakyat Jalan Tangsi Kuala lumpur. Pembukaan perniagaan Ar-Rahnu dibawah franchais Ar-Rahnu X'Change PJ Old Town, Ar-Rahnu X'Change Sg Besi Ar-Rahnu X'Change Taman Selaseh Ar Rahnu X'Change Hulu langat Ar Rahnu X'Change Bandar Kinrara Ar Rahnu X'Change Seremban 2 Ar rahnu X'Change Kota Kemuning &amp;amp; Ar Rahnu X'Change Dengkil.Mengembangkan perniagaan dalam bidang asuhan kanak-kanak.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Cameron Highlands. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jobstreet.com.my/en/job/penyambut-tetamu-clubhouse-sekata-apartment-4425598?jobId=jobstreet-my-job-4425598&amp;amp;sectionRank=6&amp;amp;token=0~291706cb-3b70-4dd0-a248-e83faafa4cc5&amp;amp;fr=SRP%20View%20In%20New%20Ta&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Cameron Highlands" /><summary type="html">Koperasi Kakitangan Bank Rakyat Berhad is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the PENYAMBUT TETAMU CLUBHOUSE SEKATA APARTMENT which positioned at Cameron Highlands</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott International Vacancies Paymaster (Contract)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/paymaster-contract-mariot-international-205197/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott International Vacancies Paymaster (Contract)" /><published>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/paymaster-contract-mariot-international-205197</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/paymaster-contract-mariot-international-205197/">&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Paymaster (Contract)&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Job Description :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category&lt;/b&gt; Finance and Accounting&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt; The Westin Desaru Coast Resort, Jalan Pantai 3, Desaru Coast, Bandar Penawar, Desaru, Malaysia, Malaysia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brand&lt;/b&gt; Westin Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt; Part-time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relocation&lt;/b&gt; No&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Type&lt;/b&gt; Non-Management/Hourly&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Your Journey With Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Westin, we are committed to empowering the well-being of our guests by providing a refreshing environment, thoughtful amenities, and revitalizing programming to help ensure that they leave feeling better than when they arrived. We recognize that travel can be disruptive to our guests&amp;#8217; well-being, and we&amp;#8217;re energized to assist as partners in helping them maintain control and soaring above it all while on the road. Everything we do is designed to help guests be at their best, and they appreciate our supportive attitude, anticipatory service and extensive knowledge on how to best assist them throughout their stay. We are looking for dynamic people who are excited to join the team and ready to jump into any situation to give a helping hand. If you&amp;#8217;re someone who has is positive, adaptable and intuitive, and has a genuine interest in the well-being of others around you, we invite you to discover how at Westin, together we can rise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check figures, postings, and documents for correct entry, mathematical accuracy, and proper codes. Organize, secure, and maintain all files, records, cash and cash equivalents in accordance with policies and procedures. Record, store, access, and/or analyze computerized financial information. Maintain accurate electronic spreadsheets for financial and accounting data. Classify, code, and summarize numerical and financial data to compile and keep financial records, using journals, ledgers, and/or computers. Prepare, maintain, and distribute statistical, financial, accounting, auditing, or payroll reports and tables. Complete period-end closing procedures and reports as specified. Prepare, review, reconcile, and issue bills, invoices, and account statements according to company procedures.&lt;br /&gt;Follow all company policies and procedures; ensure uniform and personal appearance are clean and professional; maintain confidentiality of proprietary information; protect company assets; protect the privacy and security of guests and coworkers. Address guests service needs in a professional, positive, and timely manner. Speak with others using clear and professional language; prepare and review written documents accurately and completely; answer telephones and emails using appropriate etiquette. Move, lift, carry, push, pull, and place objects weighing less than or equal to 10 pounds without assistance. Develop and maintain positive working relationships with others; support team to reach common goals; listen and respond appropriately to the concerns of other employees. Perform other reasonable job duties as requested by Supervisors.&lt;i&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture. Marriott International does not discriminate on the basis of disability, veteran status or any other basis protected under federal, state or local laws.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Marriott International&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=2055197&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Marriott International is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Paymaster (Contract) which positioned at Malaysia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott International Vacancies Multi Property IT Manager</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/multi-property-it-manager-mariot-international-20519/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott International Vacancies Multi Property IT Manager" /><published>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/multi-property-it-manager-mariot-international-20519</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/multi-property-it-manager-mariot-international-20519/">&lt;p&gt;Marriott International is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;Multi Property IT Manager&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Job Description :&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category&lt;/b&gt; Information Technology&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Location&lt;/b&gt; Miri Marriott Resort &amp;amp; Spa, Jalan Temenggong Datuk Oyong Lawai, Miri, Sarawak, Malaysia&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Brand&lt;/b&gt; Marriott Hotels Resorts /JW Marriott&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule&lt;/b&gt; Full-time&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relocation&lt;/b&gt; Yes&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Type&lt;/b&gt; Management&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Start Your Journey With Us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Marriott International portfolio of brands includes both JW Marriott and Marriott Hotels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Marriott Hotels&lt;/b&gt;, Marriott International&amp;#8217;s flagship brand with more than 500 global locations, is advancing the art of hosting so that our guests can travel brilliantly. As a host with Marriott Hotels, you will help keep this promise by delivering premium choices, sophisticated style, and well-crafted details. With your skills and imagination, together we will innovate and reinvent the future of travel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;JW Marriott &lt;/b&gt;is part of Marriott International's luxury portfolio and consists of more than 80 beautiful properties in gateway cities and distinctive resort locations around the world. JW believes our associates come first. Because if you&amp;#8217;re happy, our guests will be happy. It&amp;#8217;s as simple as that. Our hotels offer a work experience unlike any other, where you&amp;#8217;ll be part of a community and enjoy a true camaraderie with a diverse group of co-workers. JW creates opportunities for training, development, recognition and most importantly, a place where you can really pursue your passions in a luxury environment. Treating guests exceptionally starts with the way we take care of our associates. That&amp;#8217;s The JW Treatment&amp;#8482;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;JOB SUMMARY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a member of the property management staff, contributes advanced knowledge and skill in technology and general hospitality business knowledge to support the property and technology Information Resources objectives. Position is responsible to the property for all technology planning, decision-making, implementation, and maintenance. May manage property systems technicians and interfaces with vendors, owners, Executive Committee and property staff.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CANDIDATE PROFILE &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Education and Experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; BS/BA or equivalent work experience. Additionally, 3-5 years experience in like position.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Previous experience in IR Global Field Services or Marriott Systems Support desirable.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; System-related professional certifications desired.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CORE WORK ACTIVITIES&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ensuring Client Technology Needs are Met&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Uses computers and computer systems (including hardware and software) to program, write software, set up functions, enter data, or process information.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Monitors, verifies and manages the acquisition and maintenance of property based systems.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Analyzes information, identifies current and potential problems and proposes solutions.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Maintains, inspects and repairs equipment.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Inspects and verifies the maintenance of the equipment or the environment.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Verifies that computer and network operations are monitored at the property, backup/recovery functions are performed on scheduled basis and administration functions for hardware, operating and application systems are maintained and completed on consistent basis.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Manages IR activities to ensure the property infrastructure and applications systems are functional at all times.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Verifies solutions are consistent with the client's needs and brand specific IR environment.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Administers and maintains mail and email.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Maintains inventories and manages IT hardware/software.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides Internet support and maintenance (if applicable)&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides cable management support.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Generates systems communications for property users to introduce new applications, provide user tips, alert users of system problems and inform staff of progress or status.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Consults on specific application issues or hardware/software problems.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides feedback to Lodging IR on application functional performance and system performance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Managing Projects and Policies &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Uses relevant information and individual judgment to determine whether events or processes comply with laws, regulations, or standards.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Monitors processes and evaluating information according to SOP and LSOP requirements.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Enforces IR policies and standards protecting company hardware, software and other resources at the property.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Directs maintenance of equipment and installed software applications inventory for property ensuring compliance with licensing regulations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Maintaining Information Systems and Technology Goals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Develops specific goals and plans to prioritize, organize, and accomplish your work.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Performs an assessment of needs, ensuring compliance with brand specific standards, budget and capital requirements.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Determines priorities, schedules, plans and necessary resources to ensure completion of any property projects on schedule and according to specification.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Verifies problems are correctly reported, routed, tracked and solved, with the system user being informed of situation at all times.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Verifies proper asset management.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Performs on-site monitoring of all projects.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Verifies that regular on-going communication is happening in all areas of responsibility to create awareness of business objectives and communicates expectations, recognizes performance and produces desired business results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Demonstrating and Applying IR Knowledge &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Keeps up-to-date technically and applies new knowledge to your job.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Demonstrates knowledge of job-relevant issues, products, systems, and processes.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides technical expertise and support.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Leading IR Team &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Serves as a role model to demonstrate appropriate behaviors.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Utilizes interpersonal and communication skills to lead, influence, and encourage others; advocates sound financial/business decision making; demonstrates honesty/integrity; leads by example.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Celebrates successes and publicly recognizes the contributions of team members.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides a technical perspective to information needs along with cost/benefits understanding in an influencing role.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Managing and Conducting Human Resource Activities &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Verifies employees are treated fairly and equitably.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Verifies property policies are administered fairly and consistently.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Additional Responsibilities &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Provides information to supervisors, co-workers, and subordinates by telephone, in written form, e-mail, or in person.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Informs and/or updates the executives, the peers and the subordinates on relevant information in a timely manner.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Analyzes information and evaluates results to choose the best solution and solve problems.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Coordinates property efforts, prioritizes needs and communicates those needs to IR Shared Services and other systems staff.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;#8226; Manages vendors for property IT requirements functioning as escalation point for problem resolution.&lt;i&gt;Marriott International is an equal opportunity employer committed to hiring a diverse workforce and sustaining an inclusive culture. Marriott International does not discriminate on the basis of disability, veteran status or any other basis protected under federal, state or local laws.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;h4&gt;About &lt;span&gt;Marriott International&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monster.com.my/seeker/job-apply?id=2055199&amp;amp;autoApply=true&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Malaysia" /><summary type="html">Marriott International is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the Multi Property IT Manager which positioned at Malaysia</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel S Vacancies General Manager;Assistant General Manager</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jobs/general-manager-asistant-general-manager-hotel-s-429548/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel S Vacancies General Manager;Assistant General Manager" /><published>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-11-24T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jobs/general-manager-asistant-general-manager-hotel-s-429548</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jobs/general-manager-asistant-general-manager-hotel-s-429548/">&lt;p&gt;Hotel S is looking for new potential candidates to fill in for &lt;b&gt;General Manager;Assistant General Manager&lt;/b&gt; position. If you currently looking for new hotel job opportunities and qualified with the job desc, feel free to apply this job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2978031994&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Job Description&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing daily company operations to ensure positive, safe and profitable working environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement quality and productivity objectives to achieve company goals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure that employees follow the company standards, policies and strategies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cooperate in recruiting, training, performance evaluation, promotions, and releasing the employees&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coordinate in planning short term and long term projects, budgets, expense controls, schedules, and manpower&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop and implement staffing and business plans to achieve business target&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Evaluate key productivity indicators and implement process improvement initiatives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Address operational, technical and mechanical issues in a timely manner&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage direct reporting to Board of Directors related to financial, business, and administration matters&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop positive working relationship with the support divisions and operations team to ensure proper operational support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop operational strategy and ensure that the operational activities meet the organizational requirements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be responsible for evacuation, in case of emergency, acting as first point of contact for the team, guests and the emergency services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take responsibility for extra management tasks, as required, in the hotel manager&amp;#8217;s absence&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain personal knowledge by completing in-house training and workbooks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Always adhere to all company policies and procedures and licensing laws&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Interested parties, please send you resume with available start date and expected salary to us&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!-- adsense article--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block; text-align:center;&quot; data-ad-layout=&quot;in-article&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;fluid&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2979779768&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Company Overview&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hotel S&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Macau Hotel S, Situated on No. 14 e 16, Praca Ponte e Horta, Macau, offers boutique-style accommodation in central Macau. Only 10 &amp;#8211; 15 minutes away from Ruins of St. Paul&amp;#8217;s and A-Ma Temple. Nearby bus stop in this position direct access to the airport and other attractions. Macau Hotel S offers a variety of rooms from standard to deluxe suites, and all rooms are non-smoking and equipped with amenities including air conditioning, flat-screen TV, electric kettle, freezer, a bathroom with shower and personal care amenities etc. The hotel lobby also has Internet-enabled computers for guests and there is a Portuguese restaurant and bar. Macau Hotel S is the best choice for visitors who travel to Macau.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An International Chain hotel well situated at the heritage district of Macau, which has appointed an World Classed designer for a through renovation project and we will rebrand it in the next couple of years, the hotel will be restructured to a full range property with a roof top swimming pool, gymnasium; number of key will be reduced to 150 from the existing 178.&amp;#160;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our goal is to start a new era as a high-calibre and service oriented boutique hotel, we are now seeking for the positions below whom has the passions to join our dynamic team to achieve this forthcoming challenge.&amp;#160;Opportunities will be granted to the passionate candidates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-apply&quot;&gt;How To Apply&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you confident and feel that this job is suitable to you, go ahead take your action now. &lt;br /&gt; 
Hope you find your dream hotel job in Macau. &lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jobstreet.com.my/en/job/general-manager;assistant-general-manager-4429548?jobId=jobstreet-my-job-4429548&amp;amp;sectionRank=2&amp;amp;token=0~291706cb-3b70-4dd0-a248-e83faafa4cc5&amp;amp;fr=SRP%20View%20In%20New%20Ta&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--info&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopenner&quot;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;!-- Adsense Link --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;ins class=&quot;adsbygoogle&quot; style=&quot;display:block&quot; data-ad-client=&quot;ca-pub-8153773865804817&quot; data-ad-slot=&quot;2034935353&quot; data-ad-format=&quot;link&quot; data-full-width-responsive=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>HotelKini</name><email>myhotelkini@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Jobs" /><category term="Macau" /><summary type="html">Hotel S is currently looking for suitable person to fill in the General Manager;Assistant General Manager which positioned at Macau</summary></entry></feed>